<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<chapter version="5.0" xmlns="http://docbook.org/ns/docbook"
         xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"
         xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude"
         xmlns:svg="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"
         xmlns:m="http://www.w3.org/1998/Math/MathML"
         xmlns:html="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml"
         xmlns:db="http://docbook.org/ns/docbook">
  <title>Backend Configuration</title>

  <section>
    <title>Configuration - Sales</title>

    <para></para>

    <section>
      <title>Sales Functionality Setup</title>

      <para>The Sales section provides the administrator with the ability to
      set up the following parameters:</para>

      <itemizedlist>
        <listitem>
          <para>Sort order of total fields on the shopping cart Checkout
          page</para>
        </listitem>

        <listitem>
          <para>Reorder of items from an already created order</para>
        </listitem>

        <listitem>
          <para>Logos and an address to be displayed on PDF print-outs and
          HTML print view of invoices and packing slips</para>
        </listitem>

        <listitem>
          <para>Minimum order amount functionality</para>
        </listitem>

        <listitem>
          <para>Multi-address messages for an order or for each item in an
          order</para>
        </listitem>
      </itemizedlist>

      <para>Locate the Sales section by clicking <emphasis
      role="bold">System</emphasis> &gt; <emphasis
      role="bold">Configuration</emphasis> &gt;<emphasis
      role="bold"><emphasis> Sales </emphasis></emphasis>&gt; <emphasis
      role="bold">Sales</emphasis>.</para>

      <section>
        <title>Checkout Totals Sort Order</title>

        <para>The order of checkout totals located in the <emphasis
        role="bold">Order Review</emphasis> field group of the Checkout page
        depends on the values specified under the <emphasis
        role="bold">Checkout Totals Sort Order</emphasis> field group in the
        Sales section parameters. The values specified in this group only
        influence the display of the total fields sort order in the shopping
        cart Checkout page, they have no influence on calculation order.
        Specify the sort order values for the following fields:</para>

        <para><itemizedlist>
            <listitem>
              <para><emphasis role="bold">Subtotal</emphasis></para>
            </listitem>

            <listitem>
              <para><emphasis role="bold">Discount</emphasis></para>
            </listitem>

            <listitem>
              <para><emphasis role="bold">Shipping</emphasis></para>
            </listitem>

            <listitem>
              <para><emphasis role="bold">Fixed Product Tax</emphasis></para>
            </listitem>

            <listitem>
              <para><emphasis role="bold">Tax</emphasis></para>
            </listitem>

            <listitem>
              <para><emphasis role="bold">Grand Total</emphasis></para>
            </listitem>
          </itemizedlist><note>
            <para>A number of related parameters must be set up to include the
            <emphasis role="bold">Discount</emphasis> and <emphasis
            role="bold">Fixed Product Tax</emphasis> fields under the
            <emphasis role="bold">Order Review</emphasis> field group of the
            Checkout page. The setup of these parameters will be covered
            further on in this tutorial.</para>
          </note></para>
      </section>

      <section>
        <title>Reorder</title>

        <para>With the <emphasis role="bold">Reorder</emphasis> field, the
        administrator can specify whether the user can create an order from an
        already placed order.</para>

        <note>
          <para>Keep in mind that you cannot use the Reorder function from
          orders containing items of the <emphasis>Bundle Product</emphasis>
          and <emphasis>Configurable Product</emphasis> product types.</para>
        </note>

        <para>The user can simply reuse all the information from the initial
        order or enter some changes concerning the number of items to order,
        shipping and billing addresses, shipping and payment methods,
        etc.</para>
      </section>

      <section>
        <title>Invoice and Packing Slip Design</title>

        <para>An administrator can perform the setup of logos and an address
        to be included in HTML and PDF printed invoices and packing slips. The
        following fields help perform the design setup:</para>

        <para><itemizedlist>
            <listitem>
              <para><emphasis role="bold">Logo for PDF print-outs
              (200*50)</emphasis> - browse for an image to include on a
              printed PDF invoice. After an invoice is created, the
              administrator can locate the list of all created invoices in the
              backend by following the path <emphasis
              role="bold">Sales</emphasis> &gt; <emphasis
              role="bold">Invoices</emphasis> and select a check box for a
              single or multiple invoices. Then, in the <emphasis
              role="bold">Actions</emphasis> field, he or she needs to select
              the <emphasis>PDF Invoices</emphasis> option and click the
              <emphasis role="bold">Submit</emphasis> button.<note>
                  <para>Files of the .jpeg, .tiff, and .png formats can be
                  specified in this field.</para>
                </note></para>
            </listitem>

            <listitem>
              <para><emphasis role="bold">Logo for HTML print view</emphasis>
              - browse for an image to display on a printed HTML print preview
              and on its printed paper copy. In the frontend, the user can
              view an invoice, shipment, or refund print preview containing
              the specified in this field image. To view the list of orders,
              the registered user needs to open the My Orders page by clicking
              the <emphasis>My account</emphasis> link located in the upper
              right corner of the store page and click the <emphasis
              role="bold">My Orders</emphasis> Navigation Pane button. For the
              required order, click the <emphasis>View Order</emphasis> link.
              In the order page that opens, in the About This Order area,
              click the <emphasis>Invoices</emphasis> link. Under the shipping
              and billing addresses, click the <emphasis>Print
              Invoice</emphasis> link and view the print preview of the
              invoice containing the image specified in the <emphasis
              role="bold">Logo for HTML print view</emphasis> field of the
              backend. <note>
                  <para>The image specified in this field is also displayed on
                  the shipment and refund print previews for the selected
                  order. Images of the .jpeg, .gif, and .png file formats can
                  be specified in the <emphasis role="bold">Logo for HTML
                  print view</emphasis> field.</para>
                </note></para>

              <screenshot>
                <mediaobject>
                  <imageobject>
                    <imagedata fileref="../images/LogoForHTMLPrintView.png"></imagedata>
                  </imageobject>
                </mediaobject>
              </screenshot>
            </listitem>

            <listitem>
              <para><emphasis role="bold">Address</emphasis> - type an address
              to display on a print preview of an order invoice, shipment, or
              refund. The address can be viewed in the upper left corner of
              the print preview.</para>
            </listitem>
          </itemizedlist></para>
      </section>

      <section>
        <title>Minimum Order Amount</title>

        <para>The fields under the <emphasis role="bold">Minimum Order
        Amount</emphasis> field group let the administrator specify the
        minimum amount allowed on the order creation. When placing an order
        with the amount less than specified in the Sales section parameters,
        the user will not be able to procede to the shopping cart
        checkout.</para>

        <para><itemizedlist>
            <listitem>
              <para><emphasis role="bold">Enable</emphasis> - select this
              parameter to specify whether the Minimum Order Amount
              functionality is applied to the shopping cart.</para>
            </listitem>

            <listitem>
              <para><emphasis role="bold">Minimum amount</emphasis> - type the
              minimum amount which will be validated while adding an item to
              the shopping cart and trying to check it out. If the subtotal
              amount of ordered items in the shopping cart after a discount is
              less than that specified in this field, Magento will not allow
              the user to procede to the checkout.</para>
            </listitem>

            <listitem>
              <para><emphasis role="bold">Description message</emphasis> -
              type the message stating that the shopping cart order amount is
              less than the amount required for the checkout.</para>
            </listitem>

            <listitem>
              <para><emphasis role="bold">Error to show in shopping
              cart</emphasis> - ??? (A bug was created as it seems that this
              field is not used in the system)</para>
            </listitem>

            <listitem>
              <para><emphasis role="bold">Validate each address separately in
              multi-address checkout</emphasis> - select this check box to
              specify that for each address on an order, the minimum order
              amount will be separately validated.</para>
            </listitem>

            <listitem>
              <para><emphasis role="bold">Multi-address description
              message</emphasis> - type the message stating that the order
              amount of a shopping cart for one or all shipping addresses is
              less than the amount allowed for shopping cart checkout.</para>
            </listitem>

            <listitem>
              <para><emphasis role="bold">Multi-address error to show in
              shopping cart</emphasis> - ??? (This can be of the same issue as
              the Error to show in shopping cart field.)</para>
            </listitem>
          </itemizedlist></para>
      </section>

      <section>
        <title>Gift Messages</title>

        <para>A user is able to type a gift message for a person to get the
        shipping list if the following fields are set up by the backend
        administrator:</para>

        <para><itemizedlist>
            <listitem>
              <para><emphasis role="bold">Allow Gift Messages on Order
              Level</emphasis> - select this check box to let the user type a
              gift message for the entire order.</para>
            </listitem>

            <listitem>
              <para><emphasis role="bold">Allow Gift Messages for Order
              Items</emphasis> - select this check box to provide the user
              with the ability to type a gift message for each item in the
              user's order.</para>
            </listitem>
          </itemizedlist><note>
            <para>The user can type gift messages for either the entire order
            or for each item in the order by selecting the <emphasis
            role="bold">Do you have any gift items in your order?</emphasis>
            check box located under the <emphasis role="bold">Shipping
            Method</emphasis> field group on the Checkout page.</para>
          </note></para>
      </section>
    </section>

    <section>
      <title>Sales Emails Functionality Setup</title>

      <para>E-mail letters confirming an order, invoice, shipment, or credit
      memo can be sent to both registered customers and store guests if this
      is set up in the Sales Emails section. Here, the administrator can
      specify an e-mail sender, the templates to be used for mailing
      customers, and e-mail addresses to send a copy of a letter to. She or he
      can also specify whether the comments on an order, invoice, shipment, or
      credit memo will be sent to the customers. The following two subsections
      describe the setup of Order and Order Comments e-mails; the Invoice,
      Shipment, and Creditmemo areas are set up the same way.</para>

      <para>Locate the Sales Emails section by clicking <emphasis
      role="bold">System</emphasis> &gt; <emphasis
      role="bold">Configuration</emphasis> &gt; <emphasis
      role="bold"><emphasis>Sales</emphasis></emphasis> &gt; <emphasis
      role="bold">Sales Emails</emphasis>.</para>

      <section>
        <title>Order</title>

        <para>Set up the following parameters to send an e-mail letter for an
        order confirmation:</para>

        <para><itemizedlist>
            <listitem>
              <para><emphasis role="bold">Enabled</emphasis> - specify whether
              an e-mail letter is sent to the customer after an order is
              created.</para>
            </listitem>

            <listitem>
              <para><emphasis role="bold">New Order Confirmation Email
              Sender</emphasis> - specify an e-mail address from which a
              customer will be sent an order confirmation e-mail letter. An
              administrator is provided with the following options:</para>

              <itemizedlist>
                <listitem>
                  <para><emphasis>General contact</emphasis></para>
                </listitem>

                <listitem>
                  <para><emphasis>Sales representative</emphasis></para>
                </listitem>

                <listitem>
                  <para><emphasis>Customer support</emphasis></para>
                </listitem>

                <listitem>
                  <para><emphasis>Custom email 1</emphasis></para>
                </listitem>

                <listitem>
                  <para><emphasis>Custom email 2</emphasis></para>
                </listitem>
              </itemizedlist>

              <note>
                <para>Addresses for the specified options are defined under
                the following path: <emphasis role="bold">System</emphasis>
                &gt; <emphasis role="bold">Configuration</emphasis> &gt;
                <emphasis role="bold">General</emphasis> &gt; <emphasis
                role="bold">Store Email Addresses</emphasis>.</para>
              </note>
            </listitem>

            <listitem>
              <para><emphasis role="bold">New Order Confirmation
              Template</emphasis> - specify a template for an order
              confirmation e-mail letter. The letter based on the selected
              template will be sent to a registered customer. In the field,
              you can either leave a system template or choose your own
              customized one.</para>

              <para><note>
                  <para>Create customized templates from the Transactional
                  Emails page which can be located by clicking <emphasis
                  role="bold">System</emphasis> &gt; <emphasis
                  role="bold">Transactional Emails</emphasis>.</para>
                </note></para>
            </listitem>

            <listitem>
              <para><emphasis role="bold">New Order Confirmation Template for
              Guest</emphasis> - specify a template for an order confirmation
              e-mail letter to be sent to a store guest, that is an
              unregistered user. Here, you can also choose from a system
              template or your own customized ones.</para>
            </listitem>

            <listitem>
              <para><emphasis role="bold">Send Order Email Copy To</emphasis>
              - type an e-mail address to which a copy of an order
              confirmation letter will be sent.</para>

              <note>
                <para>If more than one address must be specified in the field,
                separate them by a comma.</para>
              </note>
            </listitem>

            <listitem>
              <para><emphasis role="bold">Send Order Email Copy
              Method</emphasis> - if you specified a single or multiple e-mail
              addresses in the <emphasis role="bold">Send Order Email Copy
              To</emphasis> field, choose whether to send a separate e-mail
              letter to each adressee or to send e-mails using the Bcc sending
              method (the <emphasis>To</emphasis> field in an e-mail letter
              contains only the addressee's e-mail address).</para>
            </listitem>
          </itemizedlist></para>
      </section>

      <section>
        <title>Order Comments</title>

        <para>The following parameters must be set up if it is required to
        send order comments to the customer or store guest:</para>

        <itemizedlist>
          <listitem>
            <para><emphasis role="bold">Enabled</emphasis> - specify whether
            it is possible to add comments on an order to the customer's order
            confirmation e-mail letter. When this parameter is enabled, the
            <emphasis role="bold">Notify Customer</emphasis> check box appears
            in the Comments History area of the Order page. Selecting the
            check box</para>
          </listitem>

          <listitem>
            <para><emphasis role="bold">Order Comment Email Sender</emphasis>
            - specify an e-mail address from which a customer will be sent an
            e-mail letter containing comments on the order. The options are:
            General contact, Sales representative, Customer support, Custom
            email 1, and Custom email 2.</para>
          </listitem>

          <listitem>
            <para><emphasis role="bold">Order Comment Email
            Template</emphasis> - specify a template for an e-mail letter to
            be sent to a registered customer. The letter based on the template
            will include the comments written in the <emphasis
            role="bold">Comments</emphasis> field of the Order page's Comments
            History area. In the field, you can choose whether to use a system
            template or a customized one created by you on the Transactional
            Emails page (<emphasis role="bold">System</emphasis> &gt;
            <emphasis role="bold">Transactional Emails</emphasis>).</para>
          </listitem>

          <listitem>
            <para><emphasis role="bold">Order Comment Email for
            Guest</emphasis> - specify a template for an e-mail letter to be
            sent to a store guest. In the field, you can specify whether a
            system or a customized template will be used as a basis for an
            e-mail letter containing comments on an order.</para>
          </listitem>

          <listitem>
            <para><emphasis role="bold">Send Order Comment Email Copy
            To</emphasis> - type an e-mail address to send a copy of an e-mail
            letter containing the comments on an order.</para>
          </listitem>

          <listitem>
            <para><emphasis role="bold">Send Order Email Copy
            Method</emphasis> - if you specified a single or multiple e-mail
            addresses in the <emphasis role="bold">Send Order Comment Email
            Copy To</emphasis> field, choose whether to send a separate e-mail
            letter to each adressee or to send e-mails using the Bcc sending
            method (the <emphasis>To</emphasis> field in an e-mail letter
            contains only the addressee's e-mail address).</para>
          </listitem>
        </itemizedlist>
      </section>
    </section>

    <section>
      <title>PDF Print-outs Functionality Setup</title>

      <para>Choose whether to display an order identification for an invoice,
      shipment, and/or credit memo's header by setting up the corresponding
      parameters under the <emphasis role="bold">Invoice</emphasis>, <emphasis
      role="bold">Shipment</emphasis>, and <emphasis role="bold">Credit
      Memo</emphasis> field groups.</para>

      <para>Locate the PDF Print-outs section by clicking <emphasis
      role="bold">System</emphasis> &gt; <emphasis
      role="bold">Configuration</emphasis> &gt; <emphasis
      role="bold"><emphasis>Sales</emphasis></emphasis> &gt; <emphasis
      role="bold">PDF Print-outs</emphasis>.</para>
    </section>

    <section>
      <title>Tax Functionality Setup</title>

      <para></para>

      <para>Locate the Tax section by clicking <emphasis
      role="bold">System</emphasis> &gt; <emphasis
      role="bold">Configuration</emphasis> &gt; <emphasis
      role="bold"><emphasis>Sales</emphasis></emphasis> &gt;<emphasis
      role="bold">Tax</emphasis>.</para>

      <section>
        <title>Tax Classes</title>

        <para>Tax class charged on a shipping amount is specified in the
        <emphasis role="bold">Tax Class for Shipping</emphasis> field. Prior
        to setting this parameter, you can create your own tax class on the
        Product Tax Class page which can be located by following the path:
        <emphasis role="bold">Sales</emphasis> &gt; <emphasis
        role="bold">Tax</emphasis> &gt; <emphasis role="bold">Product Tax
        Classes</emphasis>.</para>
      </section>

      <section>
        <title>Calculation Settings</title>

        <para></para>

        <itemizedlist>
          <listitem>
            <para><emphasis role="bold">Tax Calculation Method Based
            On</emphasis> - choose whether the tax calculation is based on one
            of the following methods:</para>

            <itemizedlist>
              <listitem>
                <para><emphasis>Unit Price</emphasis> - tax calculation is
                applied to the unit price of a single product</para>
              </listitem>

              <listitem>
                <para><emphasis>Row Total</emphasis> - tax calculation is
                applied to the total price of a single products'
                quantity</para>
              </listitem>

              <listitem>
                <para><emphasis>Total</emphasis> - tax calculation is applied
                to the total price amount of all products</para>
              </listitem>
            </itemizedlist>
          </listitem>

          <listitem>
            <para><emphasis role="bold">Tax Calculation Based On</emphasis> -
            choose whether tax calculation will be based on customer's
            shipping, billing address or based on the shipping origin.</para>
          </listitem>

          <listitem>
            <para><emphasis role="bold">Catalog Prices</emphasis> - specify
            whether product prices in the catalog include taxes.</para>
          </listitem>

          <listitem>
            <para><emphasis role="bold">Shipping Prices</emphasis> - choose
            whether shipping prices in the shopping cart include taxes.</para>
          </listitem>

          <listitem>
            <para><emphasis role="bold">Apply Customer Tax</emphasis> - choose
            whether to apply a customer tax prior to subtracting a discount
            from the subtotal or after it.</para>
          </listitem>

          <listitem>
            <para><emphasis role="bold">Apply Discount On Prices</emphasis> -
            ???</para>
          </listitem>

          <listitem>
            <para><emphasis role="bold">Apply Tax On</emphasis> - choose
            whether to apply tax calculation to a base price of an item for
            all store views or, if the price of the product varies depending
            on the store view, to a custom price for a specific store
            view.</para>
          </listitem>
        </itemizedlist>
      </section>

      <section>
        <title>Default Tax Destination Calculation</title>

        <para></para>

        <itemizedlist>
          <listitem>
            <para><emphasis role="bold">Default Country</emphasis> - </para>
          </listitem>

          <listitem>
            <para><emphasis role="bold">Default State</emphasis> - </para>
          </listitem>

          <listitem>
            <para><emphasis role="bold">Default Post Code</emphasis> - </para>
          </listitem>
        </itemizedlist>
      </section>

      <section>
        <title>Price Display Settings</title>

        <para></para>

        <itemizedlist>
          <listitem>
            <para><emphasis role="bold">Display Product Prices in
            Catalog</emphasis> - choose whether to display prices in the
            catalog with taxes included or without them. Both prices including
            and excluding taxes can also be displayed for a product in the
            catalog.</para>
          </listitem>

          <listitem>
            <para><emphasis role="bold">Display Shipping Prices</emphasis> -
            choose whether you want to display shipping prices with taxes
            included or without them. Here, you can also specify that both
            shipping prices including and excluding tax are presented in the
            </para>
          </listitem>
        </itemizedlist>
      </section>

      <section>
        <title>Shopping Cart Display Settings</title>

        <para></para>

        <itemizedlist>
          <listitem>
            <para><emphasis role="bold">Display Prices</emphasis> - choose
            whether to display product prices in the shopping cart with taxes
            included or without them. Both prices can be displayed if the
            corresponding option is selected in the field.</para>
          </listitem>

          <listitem>
            <para><emphasis role="bold">Display Subtotal</emphasis> - specify
            whether the subtotal for the products in the shopping cart include
            taxes. Both subtotals can be displayed in the shopping cart if the
            <emphasis>Including and excluding tax</emphasis> option is
            selected in the field.</para>
          </listitem>

          <listitem>
            <para><emphasis role="bold">Display Shipping Amount</emphasis> -
            choose whether shipping amount for the products in the shopping
            cart will include taxes or not. You can also see both shipping
            amounts with included and excluded taxes if the corresponding
            option is selected. </para>
          </listitem>

          <listitem>
            <para><emphasis role="bold">Include Tax in Grand Total</emphasis>
            - choose whether the grand total displayed on the shopping cart
            Checkout page will include the taxes or not. There is a
            possibility to view both grand totals with included and excluded
            taxes if the corresponding option is selected in this
            field.</para>
          </listitem>

          <listitem>
            <para><emphasis role="bold">Display full tax summary</emphasis> -
            </para>
          </listitem>

          <listitem>
            <para><emphasis role="bold">Display Zero Tax Subtotal</emphasis> -
            if the administrator enables this option, the Order Review section
            of the shopping cart Checkout page will include the zero tax
            subtotal; otherwise, if the tax equals zero for all products in
            the shopping cart, it will not be shown.</para>
          </listitem>
        </itemizedlist>
      </section>

      <section>
        <title>Orders, Invoices, Creditmemos Display Settings</title>

        <para></para>

        <itemizedlist>
          <listitem>
            <para><emphasis role="bold">Display Prices</emphasis> - choose
            whether to display product prices with taxes included or without
            them in the order/invoice/credit memo Totals area. Both prices can
            be displayed if the corresponding option is selected in the
            field.</para>
          </listitem>

          <listitem>
            <para><emphasis role="bold">Display Subtotal</emphasis> - specify
            whether the subtotal for the products in the order/invoice/credit
            memo Totals area include taxes. Both subtotals can be displayed if
            the <emphasis>Including and excluding tax</emphasis> option is
            selected in the field.</para>
          </listitem>

          <listitem>
            <para><emphasis role="bold">Display Shipping Amount</emphasis> -
            choose whether shipping amount for the products in the shopping
            cart will include taxes or not. You can also see both shipping
            amounts with included and excluded taxes if the corresponding
            option is selected.</para>
          </listitem>

          <listitem>
            <para><emphasis role="bold">Include Tax in Grand Total</emphasis>
            - </para>
          </listitem>

          <listitem>
            <para><emphasis role="bold">Display full tax summary</emphasis> -
            </para>
          </listitem>

          <listitem>
            <para><emphasis role="bold">Display Zero Tax Subtotal</emphasis> -
            </para>
          </listitem>
        </itemizedlist>
      </section>

      <section>
        <title>Fixed Product Taxes</title>

        <para></para>

        <itemizedlist>
          <listitem>
            <para><emphasis role="bold">Enable FPT</emphasis> - </para>
          </listitem>

          <listitem>
            <para><emphasis role="bold">Display Prices in Product
            Lists</emphasis> - </para>
          </listitem>

          <listitem>
            <para><emphasis role="bold">Display Prices on Product View
            Page</emphasis> - </para>
          </listitem>

          <listitem>
            <para><emphasis role="bold">Display Prices in Sales
            Modules</emphasis> - </para>
          </listitem>

          <listitem>
            <para><emphasis role="bold">Display Prices in Emails</emphasis> -
            </para>
          </listitem>

          <listitem>
            <para><emphasis role="bold">Apply Discounts to FPT</emphasis> -
            </para>
          </listitem>

          <listitem>
            <para><emphasis role="bold">Apply Tax to FPT</emphasis> - </para>
          </listitem>

          <listitem>
            <para><emphasis role="bold">Include FPT in Subtotal</emphasis> -
            </para>
          </listitem>
        </itemizedlist>
      </section>
    </section>

    <section>
      <title>Checkout Functionality Setup</title>

      <para>The Checkout section allows the administrator to set up the
      following parameters: </para>

      <itemizedlist>
        <listitem>
          <para>Checkout to different types of shipping addresses, guest
          checkout, and terms and conditions of product checkout </para>
        </listitem>

        <listitem>
          <para>Period of product availability in the shopping cart, products'
          images, and redirect to the shopping cart after adding a
          product</para>
        </listitem>

        <listitem>
          <para>My Cart link display with either the number of products or the
          quantity of items in the shopping cart specified</para>
        </listitem>

        <listitem>
          <para>Display of the Shopping Cart sidebar and the number of
          products in the Recently Added items area </para>
        </listitem>
      </itemizedlist>

      <para>Locate the Tax section by clicking <emphasis
      role="bold">System</emphasis> &gt; <emphasis
      role="bold">Configuration</emphasis> &gt; <emphasis
      role="bold"><emphasis>Sales</emphasis></emphasis> &gt; <emphasis
      role="bold">Checkout</emphasis>.</para>

      <section>
        <title>Checkout Options</title>

        <para>Among the options which are provided by this subsection are the
        ability to check out to single and multiple addresses or to multiple
        addresses only. The administrator can also choose whether to allow
        store guests to check out products and can also enable the term and
        conditionsa functionality for checking out an item.</para>

        <itemizedlist>
          <listitem>
            <para><emphasis role="bold">Enable Onepage Checkout</emphasis> -
            specify whether the user will have the ability to check out to
            both a single and multiple shipping addresses or to multiple
            shipping addresses only. If you select not to enable onepage
            checkout, the <emphasis role="bold">Procede to Checkout</emphasis>
            button no longer appears on the Shopping Cart page.</para>
          </listitem>

          <listitem>
            <para><emphasis role="bold">Allow Guest Checkout</emphasis> -
            specify whether only registered customers can perform a product
            checkout. If you choose to not allow guests to procede to product
            checkout, the Checkout Method section of the Checkout page will
            require the user to enter his or her e-mail address and password
            prior to starting the checkout process.</para>
          </listitem>

          <listitem>
            <para><emphasis role="bold">Enable Terms and Conditions</emphasis>
            - choose whether to enable the terms and conditions functionality.
            The user will need to accept the terms and conditions to be able
            to palce an order.</para>

            <note>
              <para>Make sure that store views are selected for the Terms and
              Conditions record created under <emphasis
              role="bold">Sales</emphasis> &gt; <emphasis role="bold">Terms
              and Conditions</emphasis>.</para>
            </note>
          </listitem>
        </itemizedlist>
      </section>

      <section>
        <title>Shopping Cart</title>

        <para>This parameter subsection allows the administrator to set
        several rules which will be applied to the period of product's
        availability in the shopping cart and the images that will be
        displayed for certain product types. It also provides the ability to
        direct the user to the shopping cart after a product is added.</para>

        <itemizedlist>
          <listitem>
            <para><emphasis role="bold">Quote Lifetime (days)</emphasis> -
            specify the number of days a product will be available in the
            shopping cart. In case the customer does not enter her or his
            account in the store within the period specified in the field, the
            item will be removed from the shopping cart.</para>
          </listitem>

          <listitem>
            <para><emphasis role="bold">After adding a product redirect to
            shopping cart</emphasis> - choose wether to simply add a product
            to the shopping cart and stay on the currect page or to add a
            product and be redirected to the Shopping cart page.</para>
          </listitem>

          <listitem>
            <para><emphasis role="bold">Grouped product image</emphasis> -
            choose what image to display for a product of the type Grouped
            Product. The options are as follows:</para>

            <itemizedlist>
              <listitem>
                <para>Product Thumbnail Itself</para>
              </listitem>

              <listitem>
                <para>Parent Product Thumbnail</para>
              </listitem>
            </itemizedlist>
          </listitem>

          <listitem>
            <para><emphasis role="bold">Configurable product image</emphasis>
            - choose what image to display for a product of the type
            Configurable Product. This can also be either an image of a parent
            product or of a product itself.</para>
          </listitem>
        </itemizedlist>
      </section>

      <section>
        <title>My Cart Link</title>

        <para>The My Cart link in the upper right corner of a store can
        display either the number of products in the shopping cart or the
        total quantity of items placed there. The administrator can set this
        up by selecting a corresponding option in the <emphasis
        role="bold">Display Cart Summary</emphasis> field of the My Cart Link
        section.</para>
      </section>

      <section>
        <title>Shopping Cart Sidebar</title>

        <para>The administrator can control the display of a shopping cart and
        the number of recently viewed items in the sidebar. Review the
        following fields to be able to perform this:</para>

        <para><itemizedlist>
            <listitem>
              <para><emphasis role="bold">Display Shopping Cart
              Sidebar</emphasis> - choose whether to display a shopping cart
              in the right sidebar. In case the administrator chooses to not
              display the shopping cart in the sidebar, the customer can
              locate it by clicking the My Cart link in the upper right corner
              of a store.</para>
            </listitem>

            <listitem>
              <para><emphasis role="bold">Maximum display Recently Added
              item(s)</emphasis> - specify the number of recently selected
              products to be displayed in the Recently added items
              area.</para>
            </listitem>
          </itemizedlist></para>
      </section>

      <section>
        <title>Payment Failed Emails</title>

        <para>[[For Nadia: intro sentence is required]]</para>

        <itemizedlist>
          <listitem>
            <para><emphasis role="bold">Payment Failed Email
            Receiver</emphasis> - specify an e-mail address of the receiver
            that will be sent an e-mail letter containing information about a
            failed payment. The options are: General contact, Sales
            representative, Customer support, Custom email 1, and Custom email
            2. </para>
          </listitem>

          <listitem>
            <para><emphasis role="bold">Payment Failed Email Sender</emphasis>
            - specify an e-mail address from which a receiver will be sent an
            e-mail letter containing information about the failed payment. The
            options are: General contact, Sales representative, Customer
            support, Custom email 1, and Custom email 2.</para>
          </listitem>

          <listitem>
            <para><emphasis role="bold">Payment Failed Template</emphasis> -
            specify a template for a payment failed e-mail letter. The letter
            based on the selected template will be sent to the address
            specified in the <emphasis role="bold">Payment Failed Email
            Receiver </emphasis>field. In the field, you can either leave a
            system template or choose your own customized one.</para>
          </listitem>

          <listitem>
            <para><emphasis role="bold">Send Payment Failed Email Copy
            To</emphasis> - type an e-mail address to which a copy of an
            e-mail letter stating that the payment failed will be sent.</para>

            <note>
              <para>If more than one address must be specified in the field,
              separate them by a comma.</para>
            </note>
          </listitem>

          <listitem>
            <para><emphasis role="bold">Send Payment Failed Email Copy
            Method</emphasis> - if you specified a single or multiple e-mail
            addresses in the <emphasis role="bold">Send Payment Failed Email
            Copy To</emphasis> field, choose whether to send a separate e-mail
            letter to each adressee or to send e-mails using the Bcc sending
            method (the <emphasis>To</emphasis> field in an e-mail letter
            contains only the addressee's e-mail address).</para>
          </listitem>
        </itemizedlist>
      </section>
    </section>

    <section>
      <title>Shipping Settings Functionality Setup</title>

      <para></para>

      <section>
        <title>Origin</title>

        <para></para>
      </section>

      <section>
        <title>Options</title>

        <para></para>
      </section>
    </section>

    <section>
      <title>Shipping Methods Functionality Setup</title>

      <para></para>

      <section>
        <title>Flat Rate</title>

        <para></para>
      </section>

      <section>
        <title>Table Rates</title>

        <para></para>
      </section>

      <section>
        <title>Free Shipping</title>

        <para></para>
      </section>

      <section>
        <title>UPS</title>

        <para></para>
      </section>

      <section>
        <title>USPS</title>

        <para></para>
      </section>

      <section>
        <title>FEDEX</title>

        <para></para>
      </section>

      <section>
        <title>DHL</title>

        <para></para>
      </section>
    </section>

    <section>
      <title>Google API Functionality Setup</title>

      <para></para>

      <section>
        <title>Google Analytics</title>

        <para></para>
      </section>

      <section>
        <title>Google Base</title>

        <para></para>
      </section>

      <section>
        <title>Google Checkout</title>

        <para></para>
      </section>

      <section>
        <title>Google Website Optimizer</title>

        <para></para>
      </section>

      <section>
        <title>Google Checkout Shipping - Merchant Calculated</title>

        <para></para>
      </section>

      <section>
        <title>Google Checkout Shipping - Carrier Calculated</title>

        <para></para>
      </section>

      <section>
        <title>Google Checkout Shipping - Flat Rate</title>

        <para></para>
      </section>

      <section>
        <title>Google Checkout Shipping - Digital Delivery</title>

        <para>Paybox System</para>
      </section>
    </section>

    <section>
      <title>PayPal Functionality Setup</title>

      <para></para>

      <section>
        <title>Website Payments Pro (Payflow Edition)</title>

        <para></para>
      </section>

      <section>
        <title>Website Payments Standard</title>

        <para></para>
      </section>

      <section>
        <title>Website Payments Pro</title>

        <para></para>
      </section>

      <section>
        <title>Payment Page Style</title>

        <para></para>
      </section>
    </section>

    <section>
      <title>Payment Methods Functionality Setup</title>

      <para></para>

      <section>
        <title>Saved CC</title>

        <para></para>
      </section>

      <section>
        <title>Zero Subtotal Checkout</title>

        <para></para>
      </section>

      <section>
        <title>Check / Money Order</title>

        <para></para>
      </section>

      <section>
        <title>Purchase Order</title>

        <para></para>
      </section>

      <section>
        <title>Authorize.netPayflow Pro</title>

        <para></para>
      </section>

      <section>
        <title>Paybox Direct</title>

        <para></para>
      </section>

      <section>
        <title>Protx Standard</title>

        <para></para>
      </section>

      <section>
        <title>Paybox System</title>

        <para></para>
      </section>

      <section>
        <title>PayPal Website Payments Pro - Express Checkout</title>

        <para></para>
      </section>

      <section>
        <title>PayPal Website Payments Pro - Direct Payments</title>

        <para></para>
      </section>

      <section>
        <title>PayPal Website Payments Pro Standard</title>

        <para></para>
      </section>

      <section>
        <title>PayPal Website Payments Pro (Payflow Edition) - Direct
        Payments</title>

        <para></para>
      </section>

      <section>
        <title>PayPal Website Payments Pro (Payflow Edition) - Expresse
        Checkout</title>

        <para></para>
      </section>

      <section>
        <title>eWAY Direct</title>

        <para></para>
      </section>

      <section>
        <title>eWAY Shared</title>

        <para></para>
      </section>

      <section>
        <title>eWAY 3D-Secure</title>

        <para></para>
      </section>

      <section>
        <title>ChronoPay Standard</title>

        <para></para>
      </section>

      <section>
        <title>ChronoPay Gateway</title>

        <para></para>
      </section>

      <section>
        <title>Cybermut Payment</title>

        <para></para>
      </section>

      <section>
        <title>iDEAL Basic</title>

        <para></para>
      </section>

      <section>
        <title>iDEAL Advanced</title>

        <para></para>
      </section>

      <section>
        <title>Cybersource (SOAP Toolkit)</title>

        <para></para>
      </section>

      <section>
        <title>Flo2Cash Payment Web Service</title>

        <para></para>
      </section>

      <section>
        <title>Checkout by Amazon</title>

        <para></para>
      </section>

      <section>
        <title>Amazon Simple Pay</title>

        <para></para>
      </section>

      <section>
        <title>Ogone</title>

        <para></para>
      </section>
    </section>
  </section>

  <section>
    <title>Default Values</title>

    <para></para>
  </section>
</chapter>
